<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
        <title>Tony Hosking</title>
        <description>Tony Hosking - Antony Hosking</description>
        <link>http://hosking.github.io</link>
        <atom:link href="http://hosking.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 12:49:23 +1000</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 12:49:23 +1000</pubDate>
        <ttl>60</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Writing An Abstract</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is a useful guide to writing an abstract.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Annotated example taken from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nature.com/nature/authors/gta&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt; Guide to
Authors&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-6&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-info&quot;&gt;
      One or two sentences providing a &lt;b&gt;basic introduction&lt;/b&gt; to the field,
      comprehensible to a scientist in any discipline.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-warning&quot;&gt;
      Two to three sentences of &lt;b&gt;more detailed background&lt;/b&gt;, comprehensible
      to scientists in related disciplines.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-danger&quot;&gt;
      One sentence clearly stating the &lt;b&gt;general problem&lt;/b&gt; being addressed by
      this particular study.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-success&quot;&gt;
      One sentence summarizing the main result (with the words &amp;ldquo;&lt;b&gt;here we
      show&lt;/b&gt;&amp;rdquo; or their equivalent).
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-info&quot;&gt;
      Two or three sentences explaining what the &lt;b&gt;main result&lt;/b&gt; reveals in
      direct comparison to what was thought to be the case previously, or how
      the main result adds to previous knowledge.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-warning&quot;&gt;
      One or two sentences to put the results into a more &lt;b&gt;general
      context&lt;/b&gt;.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-danger&quot;&gt;
      Two or three sentences to provide a &lt;b&gt;broader perspective&lt;/b&gt;, readily
      comprehensible to a scientist in any discipline, may be included in
      the first paragraph if the editor considers that the accessibility of
      the paper is significantly enhanced by their inclusion. Under these
      circumstances, the length of the paragraph can be up to 300
      words. (This example is 190 words without the final section, and 250
      words with it.)
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-6&quot;&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;bg-info&quot;&gt;
      During cell division, mitotic spindles are assembled by microtubule
      based motor proteins&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;.
    &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;bg-warning&quot;&gt;
      The bipolar organization of spindles is essential for proper segregation
      of chromosomes, and requires plus-end-directed homotetrameric motor
      proteins of the widely conserved kinesin-5 (BimC)
      family&lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;. Hypotheses for bipolar spindle formation include the
      &amp;lsquo;push-pull mitotic muscle&amp;rsquo; model, in which kinesin-5 and
      opposing motor proteins act between overlapping
      microtubules&lt;sup&gt;2,4,5&lt;/sup&gt;.
    &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;bg-danger&quot;&gt;
      However, the precise roles of kinesin-5 during this process are unknown.
    &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;bg-success&quot;&gt;
      Here we show that the vertebrate kinesin-5 Eg5 drives the sliding of
      microtubules depending on their relative orientation.
    &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;bg-info&quot;&gt;
      We found in controlled &lt;i&gt;in vitro&lt;/i&gt; assays that Eg5 has the remarkable
      capability of simultaneously moving at ~20 nm s&lt;sup&gt;-1&lt;/sup&gt; towards the
      plus-ends of each of the two microtubules it crosslinks. For anti-parallel
      microtubules, this results in relative sliding at ~40 nm s&lt;sup&gt;-1&lt;/sup&gt;,
      comparable to spindle pole separation rates &lt;i&gt;in vivo&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt;.
      Furthermore, we found that Eg5 can tether microtubule plus-ends,
      suggesting an additional microtubule-binding mode for Eg5.
    &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;bg-warning&quot;&gt;
      Our results demonstrate how members of the kinesin-5 family are likely to
      function in mitosis, pushing apart interpolar microtubules as well as
      recruiting microtubules into bundles that are subsequently polarized by
      relative sliding.
    &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;bg-danger&quot;&gt;
      We anticipate our assay to be a starting point for more sophisticated
      &lt;i&gt;in vitro&lt;/i&gt; models of mitotic spindles. For example, the individual
      and combined action of multiple mitotic motors could be tested,
      including minus-end-directed motors opposing Eg5 motility. Furthermore,
      Eg5 inhibition is a major target of anti-cancer drug development, and a
      well-defined and quantitative assay for motor function will be relevant
      for such developments.
    &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hosking.github.io/lessons/2015/07/23/writing-an-abstract</link>
                <guid>http://hosking.github.io/lessons/2015/07/23/writing-an-abstract</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
